Better head to work.
It's about 60,000 a month
for cutting down trees, right?
Then there's the kidney I sold.
That was 1.2 million.
My right eye was 300,000.
Sold one of my nuts...
How much was that, again?
I think... not even 100,000.
And I still owe...
About 38,040,000 yen.
I heard you, Pochita.
Let's kill this thing already.
A dead devil's usually good
for about 300,000...
Devil hunting pays the best, easy.
Gotta be the Tomato Devil.
He'll revive from the seeds,
so you'll wanna burn those.
Nice work, Denji.
This carcass will bring in a fair
price on the black market.
I'll pay you 400,000.
Hey, thanks!
After what you owe and
the interest, that leaves 170,000.
So after the finder's fee, admin fee,
management costs, and so on...
Leaves me with 70,000.
After the water bill,
and some other stuff I owe...
Funny how that works.
I've got 1,800 yen left.
No food at home, and this is gonna
have to last us a month, so...
Pochita, looks like dinner's
gonna be a slice of bread.
Why hire a brat like that to hunt devils?
He's paying off what he owes us.
Well, technically, it was
his deadbeat old man's debt.
And a kid with a pet devil
can get the job done?
The thing about real devil hunters is...
They don't pass devil
carcasses onto the yakuza.
Besides, the best thing about Denji
is he does what he's told.
Hey, dog!
I'll give you 100 yen to eat this cigarette.
For real?
Don't mind if I do.
We'll be in touch
when there's another devil.
Try and run, and you're pig slop.
That'll keep us for another three days.
The other day I heard...
That normally, people put jam
on their bread, before eating it.
Normal's just a dream for us, though.
Doubt I'll pay off this debt before I die.
Probably gonna die without
ever having a girlfriend, too.
Not like I could invite a girl to this dump.
No money to go on dates, either.
If I could have one dream come true...
I wanna score with a girl before I die.
Bastard hung himself without
paying this month's installment first.
Boy, you've got until tomorrow
to put 700,000 together.
You can beg for it, whore yourself out...
I don't care. Get it done.
Otherwise, we chop you up and sell the bits.
A ch-chainsaw...?
A devil.
If you're gonna kill me, just do it.
I'm dead either way.
It's hurt?
You're gonna die, too?
Bite me!
I heard that drinking blood heals a devil.
If you don't wanna die, bite me!
My blood's not free, though. This is a deal!
I'll help you...
So, you help me.
Because I don't wanna die, after all.
Why don't you hire me as a devil hunter?
Too hungry to sleep.
When I can't sleep,
I start thinking about money,
and then it's even harder to sleep.
I know what dream I wanna have when I sleep.
Gonna put jam on my bread,
and share it with you.
Then I'm gonna flirt with a girl...
I'll play video games with her, and then
we'll fall asleep hugging each other.
Sounds sweet, right?
Y'know, I heard my mom died from some
heart disease that made her cough up blood.
Got a devil for you, Denji. Time for work.
Wish they'd at least let me dream...
There's a devil in here, huh?
I don't see anything.
You think it's hiding?
Or maybe it left already?
Denji, my boy... we're pretty
grateful to you, y'know?
Yeah?
You're as loyal as a dog,
and you work for cheap like one, too.
Only problem with dogs
is I can't stand the stench.
Even yakuza think about getting bigger
and making more money, kid.
So we did like you,
and made a deal with a devil.
We wanted demonic power...
And I want devil hunters...
Dead!
Y'know, little devil hunter,
these guys are dumb as hell.
Total suckers!
I offer them a bit of demonic power,
and they offer to become my slaves...
Even though the power
turns them into zombies.
See, because I'm the Zombie Devil.
And I hate devil hunters, because you
go around killing us devils.
So I'm gonna kill you.
Boys, tear him apart
and toss him in the trash.
Shit!
How do I get out of here?
Get off!
It's not like I'm asking to be rich.
All I want is a normal life!
And I can't even have that?!
Pochita...
Pochita!
Pochita, time for work.
Pochita, there's a good chance
I'm gonna die fighting a devil.
My only regret would be
leaving you on your own.
You could end up starving to death...
Or some other devil hunter might kill you.
I've heard some devils
can take over dead bodies.
If that's something you can do...
then I want you to have my body.
The yakuza won't be on your case
if you wait until I've been buried, right?
And then you could move
out of here... and then...
Yeah.
I want you to live a normal life,
and die a normal death.
You've gotta make my dream come true.
Pochita?
Did you take my body, like I said?
I always loved hearing you talk
about your dreams, Denji.
Here's the deal. I'll give you my heart...
And in exchange, I want you
to show me your dream.
Pochita?!
I'm not hurt?
Pochita...?
What is this?
You're alive after being sliced up?
Why? Gross!
I seriously hate devil hunters.
Guys, go ahead and eat him.
These guys had plenty already,
so why'd they want even more?
Am I the same?
I wasn't satisfied with
the happiness I had with Pochita.
I kept dreaming about a better life.
I guess we all dream
about stuff like that, huh?
I can't blame you, then.
And I won't, but...
If you get in our way?
You'll die!
He's bound to stay dead after being eaten.
What are you?!
Did that devil runt take your body?!
That means you're one of us!
Ow...
It hurts!
Stay away!
Move!
Stay back! Back! Get away!
Stay away! Don't do it!
Don't come near me!
Die!
I guess you guys went full devil, huh?
Well, you hired me to be a devil hunter.
So, I better kill all the devils, right?!
Oh, yeah!
Once you're all dead...
I won't owe a damn thing!
Someone got here before us.
There's still one alive.
You've got a strange smell.
Not like a human or a devil.
I take it you did this?
H-Hug me...
He's human.
Any chance he's possessed?
No.
I can tell who's possessed
with a look at their face.
I came here to kill the Zombie Devil.
I'm a devil hunter with Public Safety.
You have two options:
I can kill you like a devil,
or I can keep you as a human.
If I keep you, I'll make sure you're fed.
When you say that...
Like, what's for breakfast?
Bread with butter and jam, salad, coffee...
And then maybe something
for dessert, I think?
That sounds awesome.